<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>plants on Lilie Artsci's blog</title><link>https://lilie-artsci.github.io/tags/plants/</link><description>Recent content in plants on Lilie Artsci's blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lilie-artsci.github.io/tags/plants/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Colored Tree</title><link>https://lilie-artsci.github.io/2022/08/colored-tree/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lilie-artsci.github.io/2022/08/colored-tree/</guid><description>Hello,
I often like to look at books and encyclopedia on nature to find inspiration.
For this one, I took the inspiration from the picture of a tree in the Serengeti savanna, where a bird called black-capped social weaver likes to make its nest. Many birds do so on the same tree (hence the name &amp;ldquo;social&amp;rdquo;), and the nests look like balls hanging a bit like in a Christmas tree :)</description></item><item><title>Autumn Perfume</title><link>https://lilie-artsci.github.io/2021/10/autumn-perfume/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lilie-artsci.github.io/2021/10/autumn-perfume/</guid><description>Hello,
Last weekend, I went to the parc and was happy to see the rich colors autumn is giving to the trees. I collected a few leaves and branches and it inspired me to this painting.</description></item><item><title>Plant and Tree Doodles</title><link>https://lilie-artsci.github.io/2021/07/plant-and-tree-doodles/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lilie-artsci.github.io/2021/07/plant-and-tree-doodles/</guid><description>Hello,
This post continues on the topic of doodling, this time with plants and trees.
Plant and Tree Doodles Again, I started by taking ideas over the web, and collecting doodles.
Composition of tree doodles Now, we can turn those doodles into a unique composition. And voilà!
Transforming photos into doodles We can also browse the web for actual photos of trees and transform them into doodles. This can be very fun too!</description></item><item><title>Flower Doodles</title><link>https://lilie-artsci.github.io/2021/06/flower-doodles/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lilie-artsci.github.io/2021/06/flower-doodles/</guid><description>Hello,
Today, I will show a few doodles I did with flowers and plants, with inspirations from web searches and above all from Creations CeeCee&amp;rsquo;s YouTube videos.
Flower Doodles The idea that CeeCee gives (and which I loved) is to make our own booklet of doodles, that we can use later in compositions.
Composition of flower doodles Now, we can turn those doodles into a unique composition. And voilà!</description></item></channel></rss>