<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>painting on Lilie Artsci's blog</title><link>https://lilie-artsci.github.io/tags/painting/</link><description>Recent content in painting on Lilie Artsci's blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lilie-artsci.github.io/tags/painting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Nice</title><link>https://lilie-artsci.github.io/2023/05/nice/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lilie-artsci.github.io/2023/05/nice/</guid><description>Hello!
I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on a pop-up book of the places I&amp;rsquo;ve lived in, for the Domestika class by Sylvia Hijano, which I&amp;rsquo;m really enjoying!
I just finished a page on Nice, France, where I spent around 8 years. Here are the details of the page.
Cimiez neighborhood, which is the area near which I used to live, with the roman arena, the Matisse museum and the monastery: And here is the Negresco, a luxuary hotel near the beach (the lines are for the popup folding):</description></item><item><title>Spring Air</title><link>https://lilie-artsci.github.io/2023/04/spring-air/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lilie-artsci.github.io/2023/04/spring-air/</guid><description>Hello!
These last few weeks, I&amp;rsquo;ve enjoyed watching nature being reborn, flowers and trees blooming, taking moments outside feeling the sun on the face&amp;hellip;
And it has inspired me this drawing, while I was sitting on my terrace and watching the plants I have and the neighbours&amp;rsquo; too.
I hope you all enjoy spring time!</description></item><item><title>Doodle sketchbook</title><link>https://lilie-artsci.github.io/2023/01/doodle-sketchbook/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lilie-artsci.github.io/2023/01/doodle-sketchbook/</guid><description>Hello,
On several of her YouTube&amp;rsquo;s videos, Creations CeeCee gives the very good advice of making doodling sketchbooks. It consits in painting circles or vague shapes when we have remaining paint, and drawing anything that comes to mind on top of it once it&amp;rsquo;s dry.
I tested that, and I really liked having a sketchbook like that always close by. It can be really fun, or relaxing depending on what we draw, and it&amp;rsquo;s a great activity for the kids too!</description></item><item><title>Corsica landscape</title><link>https://lilie-artsci.github.io/2022/09/corsica-landscape/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lilie-artsci.github.io/2022/09/corsica-landscape/</guid><description>Hello,
I&amp;rsquo;ve been practising lately how to paint landscapes with watercolour, especially sea landscapes. I struggled quite a bit at first, with the colours and the details, but I&amp;rsquo;m quite happy with my last attempt.
Here is the original photo I took for inspiration, taken last April in Cargèse, Corsica:
As I mentioned, my first attempts were not very conclusive, especially the second one which I painted on site, I put them here to show the progress I&amp;rsquo;ve made over the trials:</description></item></channel></rss>