<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Landscape on Lilie Artsci&#39;s blog</title>
    <link>https://lilie-artsci.github.io/categories/landscape/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Landscape on Lilie Artsci&#39;s blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://lilie-artsci.github.io/categories/landscape/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Pop-up book</title>
      <link>https://lilie-artsci.github.io/2024/07/pop-up-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lilie-artsci.github.io/2024/07/pop-up-book/</guid>
      <description>Hey!&#xA;I finally finished my pop-up book after 3 years! It took me a lot of time to figure out which buildings I wanted to make pop, and how I was able to do so. But I&amp;rsquo;m super proud and happy of the result!&#xA;Each page shows a place I&amp;rsquo;ve lived in for at least a few weeks: Rouen, Mexico, Madrid, Barcelona, New York State, Tokyo and Nice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nice</title>
      <link>https://lilie-artsci.github.io/2023/05/nice/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lilie-artsci.github.io/2023/05/nice/</guid>
      <description>Hello!&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on a pop-up book of the places I&amp;rsquo;ve lived in, for the Domestika class by Sylvia Hijano, which I&amp;rsquo;m really enjoying!&#xA;I just finished a page on Nice, France, where I spent around 8 years. Here are the details of the page.&#xA;Cimiez neighborhood, which is the area near which I used to live, with the roman arena, the Matisse museum and the monastery: And here is the Negresco, a luxuary hotel near the beach (the lines are for the popup folding): </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corsica landscape</title>
      <link>https://lilie-artsci.github.io/2022/09/corsica-landscape/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lilie-artsci.github.io/2022/09/corsica-landscape/</guid>
      <description>Hello,&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;ve been practising lately how to paint landscapes with watercolour, especially sea landscapes. I struggled quite a bit at first, with the colours and the details, but I&amp;rsquo;m quite happy with my last attempt.&#xA;Here is the original photo I took for inspiration, taken last April in Cargèse, Corsica:&#xA;As I mentioned, my first attempts were not very conclusive, especially the second one which I painted on site, I put them here to show the progress I&amp;rsquo;ve made over the trials:</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
