<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Lilie Artsci's blog</title><link>https://lilie-artsci.github.io/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Lilie Artsci's blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lilie-artsci.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Corsica landscape</title><link>https://lilie-artsci.github.io/2022/09/corsica-landscape/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lilie-artsci.github.io/2022/09/corsica-landscape/</guid><description>Hello,
I&amp;rsquo;ve been practising lately how to paint landscapes with watercolour, especially sea landscapes. I struggled quite a bit at first, with the colours and the details, but I&amp;rsquo;m quite happy with my last attempt.
Here is the original photo I took for inspiration, taken last April in Cargèse, Corsica:
As I mentioned, my first attempts were not very conclusive, especially the second one which I painted on site, I put them here to show the progress I&amp;rsquo;ve made over the trials:</description></item><item><title>Colored Tree</title><link>https://lilie-artsci.github.io/2022/08/colored-tree/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lilie-artsci.github.io/2022/08/colored-tree/</guid><description>Hello,
I often like to look at books and encyclopedia on nature to find inspiration.
For this one, I took the inspiration from the picture of a tree in the Serengeti savanna, where a bird called black-capped social weaver likes to make its nest. Many birds do so on the same tree (hence the name &amp;ldquo;social&amp;rdquo;), and the nests look like balls hanging a bit like in a Christmas tree :)</description></item><item><title>Hedy Lamarr</title><link>https://lilie-artsci.github.io/2022/04/hedy-lamarr/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lilie-artsci.github.io/2022/04/hedy-lamarr/</guid><description>Hey there,
This month, ONU Femmes France celebrates a fascinating woman. We all know her face, we&amp;rsquo;ve seen her since childhood, but few of us know her name. I give you: Hedy Lamarr, the woman who inspired Disney&amp;rsquo;s Snow White.
She was an Austrian actress and movie producer, and was considered the most beautiful woman. But the reason I want to talk about her today is that she was also an inventor.</description></item><item><title>Insects</title><link>https://lilie-artsci.github.io/2022/03/insects/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lilie-artsci.github.io/2022/03/insects/</guid><description>Hey there,
I recently took an online class by Laura McKendry, whose style I love and I find so loose and fresh, and for that class I made a couple of drawings about insects. I discovered how much fun they are to paint or draw!
This first one I painted with watercolor the basic shape I wanted to do, and then I drawed with pencils on top.
In this second one, I tried to paint them walking in different directions and to look more lively :)</description></item><item><title>Psycho-cat</title><link>https://lilie-artsci.github.io/2022/01/psycho-cat/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lilie-artsci.github.io/2022/01/psycho-cat/</guid><description>Hey!
Here is a small drawing of my cat, whose favorite posture is to lie on the back.
She&amp;rsquo;s often in that weird mood in-between cuddly and psycho-cat, lying a trap full of claws when we try to pet it :)</description></item><item><title>Japanese style characters</title><link>https://lilie-artsci.github.io/2021/12/japanese-style-characters/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lilie-artsci.github.io/2021/12/japanese-style-characters/</guid><description>Hi there!
A few months ago, I took the Domestika class &amp;ldquo;Watercolor illustration with Japanese influence&amp;rdquo; by Flor Kaneshiro. It inspired me to design the following characters. For the little girl in kimono, I took inspiration with a kimono I bought in Japan. The panda is more in Chinese style.</description></item><item><title>Ada Lovelace Day</title><link>https://lilie-artsci.github.io/2021/10/ada-lovelace-day/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lilie-artsci.github.io/2021/10/ada-lovelace-day/</guid><description>Hello,
Last Tuesday, October 12, was Ada Lovelace Day. Many other artists shared their illustration of Ada Lovelace, as well as a short biography of her. I wanted to share mine as well.
As many said before me, she was a Mathematician and the first person ever to design a computer program when computers didn&amp;rsquo;t even exist, and at a time where it was often believed that women were only interested in &amp;ldquo;futile things&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Autumn Perfume</title><link>https://lilie-artsci.github.io/2021/10/autumn-perfume/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lilie-artsci.github.io/2021/10/autumn-perfume/</guid><description>Hello,
Last weekend, I went to the parc and was happy to see the rich colors autumn is giving to the trees. I collected a few leaves and branches and it inspired me to this painting.</description></item><item><title>Plant and Tree Doodles</title><link>https://lilie-artsci.github.io/2021/07/plant-and-tree-doodles/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lilie-artsci.github.io/2021/07/plant-and-tree-doodles/</guid><description>Hello,
This post continues on the topic of doodling, this time with plants and trees.
Plant and Tree Doodles Again, I started by taking ideas over the web, and collecting doodles.
Composition of tree doodles Now, we can turn those doodles into a unique composition. And voilà!
Transforming photos into doodles We can also browse the web for actual photos of trees and transform them into doodles. This can be very fun too!</description></item><item><title>Flower Doodles</title><link>https://lilie-artsci.github.io/2021/06/flower-doodles/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lilie-artsci.github.io/2021/06/flower-doodles/</guid><description>Hello,
Today, I will show a few doodles I did with flowers and plants, with inspirations from web searches and above all from Creations CeeCee&amp;rsquo;s YouTube videos.
Flower Doodles The idea that CeeCee gives (and which I loved) is to make our own booklet of doodles, that we can use later in compositions.
Composition of flower doodles Now, we can turn those doodles into a unique composition. And voilà!</description></item><item><title>Frogs</title><link>https://lilie-artsci.github.io/2021/06/frogs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lilie-artsci.github.io/2021/06/frogs/</guid><description>Hello,
This post will be about frogs :)
Blue dendrobate During a visit to a zoological garden, I discovered the amazingly blue dendrobate. I then tried to capture it with watercolor ink (which I think I managed quite well ;)).
From real to abstract Being confined at home, I had time to work on improving my drawing skills, and experimented more abstract representations of pictures of animals. So I took my animal encyclopedia and picked the tree frog.</description></item><item><title>Inktober 2020 part 2</title><link>https://lilie-artsci.github.io/2020/11/inktober-2020-part-2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lilie-artsci.github.io/2020/11/inktober-2020-part-2/</guid><description>Hello,
So I didn&amp;rsquo;t have much time to work on the challenge in the end&amp;hellip; But I did a few more to share. #inktober
No. 5: Blade For this drawing, I found inspiration by looking at images of katana online, and I stumbled upon that photo which I liked very much.
No.6: Rodent This one was actually rather easy, as I spent quite some time drawing animals and plants from an encyclopedia during the first confinement.</description></item><item><title>Inktober 2020</title><link>https://lilie-artsci.github.io/2020/10/inktober-2020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lilie-artsci.github.io/2020/10/inktober-2020/</guid><description>Hello,
This year, I am doing Inktober, this challenge of making one drawing in ink each day. I thought it would be a good reason to start sharing what I have been doing since I got back to drawing and painting. I am a little late for the challenge, I started only a few days ago, but that does not matter. The idea is to take a month to improve ourselves.</description></item></channel></rss>