<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>english on Lilie Artsci&#39;s blog</title>
    <link>https://example.org/tags/english/</link>
    <description>Recent content in english on Lilie Artsci&#39;s blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.org/tags/english/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to Lilie Artsci&#39;s blog</title>
      <link>https://example.org/2021/10/welcome-to-lilie-artscis-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/2021/10/welcome-to-lilie-artscis-blog/</guid>
      <description>Hello, I&amp;rsquo;m Lilie. Welcome to my blog on arts and science, sometimes mixed together. You will find here some of my drawings and things I find cool in science.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plant and Tree Doodles</title>
      <link>https://example.org/2021/07/plant-and-tree-doodles/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/2021/07/plant-and-tree-doodles/</guid>
      <description>Hello,
This post continues on the topic of doodling, this time with plants and trees.
Plant and Tree Doodles Again, I started by taking ideas over the web, and collecting doodles.
Composition of tree doodles Now, we can turn those doodles into a unique composition. And voilà!
Transforming photos into doodles We can also browse the web for actual photos of trees and transform them into doodles. This can be very fun too!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flower Doodles</title>
      <link>https://example.org/2021/06/flower-doodles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/2021/06/flower-doodles/</guid>
      <description>Hello,
Today, I will show a few doodles I did with flowers and plants, with inspirations from web searches and above all from Creations CeeCee&amp;rsquo;s YouTube videos.
Flower Doodles The idea that CeeCee gives (and which I loved) is to make our own booklet of doodles, that we can use later in compositions.
Composition of flower doodles Now, we can turn those doodles into a unique composition. And voilà!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frogs</title>
      <link>https://example.org/2021/06/frogs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/2021/06/frogs/</guid>
      <description>Hello,
This post will be about frogs :)
Blue dendrobate During a visit to Monaco&amp;rsquo;s zoological garden, I discovered the amazingly blue dendrobate. I then tried to capture it with watercolor ink (which I think I managed quite well ;)).
From real to abstract Being confined at home, I had time to work on improving my drawing skills, and experimented more abstract representations of pictures of animals. So I took my animal encyclopedia and picked the tree frog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inktober 2020 part 2</title>
      <link>https://example.org/2020/11/inktober-2020-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/2020/11/inktober-2020-part-2/</guid>
      <description>Hello,
So I didn&amp;rsquo;t have much time to work on the challenge in the end&amp;hellip; But I did a few more to share. #inktober
No. 5: Blade For this drawing, I found inspiration by looking at images of katana online, and I stumbled upon that photowhich I liked very much.
No.6: Rodent This one was actually rather easy, as I spent quite some time drawing animals and plants from an encyclopedia during the first confinement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inktober 2020</title>
      <link>https://example.org/2020/10/inktober-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/2020/10/inktober-2020/</guid>
      <description>Hello,
This year, I am doing Inktober, this challenge of making one drawing in ink each day. I thought it would be a good reason to start sharing what I have been doing since I got back to drawing and painting. I am a little late for the challenge, I started only a few days ago, but that does not matter. The idea is to take a month to improve ourselves.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
